Guide to the Lewis Carroll Society of North America Archive, 1974-2015 MSS.148
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Miscellanous Records
  - Subseries E: Maxine G. Schaefer Children's Outreach Program
    - Maxine G. Schaefer Children's Outreach Program, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Subseries F: LCSNA Brochures
    - LCSNA Brochures, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Subseries G: Donations to the LCSNA Archives
    - Dr. Hugues Debailly's Dissertation, 1997; 4 sheets of microfiche in paper sleeve (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Memoria Technica" by Lorraine Levender Whittlesey, sound recording, with liner notes and paper program., 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      148.0004. Compact Disc, in plastic jewel case.
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous offprints and other assorted materials
    - Miscellaneous offprints and other assorted materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Subseries I: Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter"
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Subseries J: LCSNA Archives Assemblage Records
    - LCSNA Archives Assemblage Records, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - LCSNA Archives Assemblage Records, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Accretion 2012 - Series I: Constitution and Organic Documents
  - Early letters and bulletins from Stan Marx on formation of a American Lewis Carroll Society, including letter officially announcing the establishment of the Society, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Accretion 2012 - Series II: Publications
  - Subseries A: Books
    - Elizabeth Sewell's Lewis Carroll: Voices from France. Transcription from the original typescript by Alan and Alison Tannenbaum., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Elizabeth Sewell's Lewis Carroll: Voices from France. Original material returned from the printer, Sheridan Books, Inc., 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subseries F: Publication Contracts & Documents
    - Documents on transfer of copyright of In Memoriam Charles Lutwidge Dodgson, 1832-1898 from Charlie Lovett and August A. Imholtz, Jr. to LCSNA, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Accretion 2012 - Series III: Membership Records
  - Subseries C: Samples of Secretary-Member Correspondence
    - Ellie Luchinsky's LCSNA secretary's files, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - Correspondence from Martin Gardner to Jason Duran, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from August Imholz to David Smith, Andy Malcolm, Professor Gully, Pat Carroll, Harriet Lynn, Dorrit Billman, and Agnes Barbier, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Accretion 2012 - Series VII: Miscellaneous Records
  - Subseries A: Photographs from Selected Meetings and Events
    - CD-ROM scans of Alice's visit to Columbia, the centenary program, photographs of Carroll, photographs of Alice, etc., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: LCSNA Auction Records
    - Ellie Luchinsky's auction planning notebook, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Subseries G: Donations to the LCSNA
    - Helen Weaver's letter to Ellie Luchinsky on the files of her father, Warren Weaver, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Catalog of Joe Christopher's Lewis Carroll Collection, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Printed facsimile of Lewis Carroll Centenary Celebration, May 4, 1932, Columbia University, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Accretion 2016
  Scope and Contents
  This accretion contains documents that date between 2007 and 2015, including correspondence, receipts, and a few Alice's Adventures in Wonderland pins, one of which is from the 150th Anniversary. The correspondence within the accretion consists of both cards and letters, many of which are addressed to Clare Imholtz.
  Arrangement
  This accretion has not been arranged by an archivist; materials are arranged in the order in which they were received.
  - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 2007-2012 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Membership Survey Responses, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Alice in Wonderland Pins, circa 2015 (Box 7)
- Oversize: Series IV, General Meeting Notes
  - General Meeting Notes, October 28, 1974. University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Box 5, Folder 7)
    General
    Offsite barcode: 31142042240187
  - General Meeting Notes, April 22, 1995. Butler Library, Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Oversize: Series V, Executive and Publications Committee Records
  - December 11, 1982- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - November 17, 1984- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - November 9, 1985- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - April 26, 1986- Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - December 15, 1986- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - April 25, 1987- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - October 24, 1897- Executive Committee Meeting, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - May 14, 1988- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - May 6, 1989- Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - October 21, 1989- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - May 12, 1990- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - October 20, 1990- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - April 20, 1991- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Oversize: Series VII, Miscellaneous Records
  - Subseries I: Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter"
    - Contributions to and draft versions of "The Knight Letter", undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Unprocessed Ephemera and Correspondence, 1989-1999 (Box 8)